<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Analyser</string>
    <string name="version_x">Version %1$s</string>
    <string name="common_back">Back</string>

    <!--  BOTTOM NAVIGATION  -->
    <string name="nav_home">Home</string>
    <string name="nav_device">Device</string>
    <string name="nav_apps">Apps</string>
    <string name="nav_settings">Settings</string>

    <!--  HOME SCREEN  -->
    <string name="home_empty_hint">Long-press a card on the Device screen to add it here</string>
    <string name="home_remove_widget">Remove card</string>
    <string name="home_sensor_unavailable">Sensor unavailable on this device</string>

    <!--  SETTINGS SCREEN  -->
    <string name="settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_appearance">Appearance</string>
    <string name="settings_appearance_summary">Theme and app colors</string>
    <string name="settings_device_info">Device info</string>
    <string name="settings_device_info_summary">Temperature unit, sensor view</string>
    <string name="settings_home">Home screen</string>
    <string name="settings_home_summary">Card grid layout</string>
    <string name="settings_about">About app</string>
    <string name="settings_about_summary">Version, author, repository</string>
    <string name="settings_theme_colors">Theme colors</string>
    <string name="settings_dark_mode">Dark mode</string>
    <string name="settings_dark_follow_system">System</string>
    <string name="settings_dark_light">Light</string>
    <string name="settings_dark_dark">Dark</string>
    <string name="settings_pure_black">Pure black</string>
    <string name="settings_pure_black_description">Fully black background in dark mode, saves battery on OLED screens</string>
    <string name="settings_home_columns">Columns</string>
    <string name="settings_home_columns_description">Number of columns on the home screen grid</string>
    <string name="settings_temperature_unit">Temperature unit</string>
    <string name="settings_simple_sensor_view">Use simple sensor view</string>
    <string name="settings_simple_sensor_view_description">Show only the sensor name and its value</string>
    <string name="settings_sensor_units">Show sensor units</string>
    <string name="settings_sensor_units_description">Display the measurement unit after sensor values</string>
    <string name="temperature_unit_celsius">Celsius (°C)</string>
    <string name="temperature_unit_fahrenheit">Fahrenheit (°F)</string>
    <string name="temperature_unit_kelvin">Kelvin (K)</string>
    <string name="theme_dakils_analyser">Dakil\'s Analyser</string>
    <string name="theme_dynamic">System colors</string>
    <string name="theme_ocean">Ocean</string>
    <string name="theme_lavender">Lavender</string>
    <string name="theme_sunset">Sunset</string>
    <string name="theme_rose">Rose</string>
    <string name="theme_teal">Teal</string>

    <!--  ABOUT DIALOG  -->
    <string name="about_title">About Analyser</string>
    <string name="about_how_it_works">How it works</string>
    <string name="about_how_it_works_description">App Analyser detects the core tech stack of your installed applications by reading their APK signatures dynamically without fully extracting them. It maps file names to determine the underlying framework.</string>
    <string name="about_repository">Repository</string>
    <string name="about_author">Author</string>
    <string name="about_close">Close</string>

    <!--  APP LIST SCREEN  -->
    <string name="app_list_show_system_apps">Show system apps</string>
    <string name="app_list_search_apps">Search apps...</string>
    <string name="app_list_system_app_label">System app</string>

    <!--  APP DETAILS SCREEN  -->
    <string name="app_details_title">App details</string>
    <string name="app_details_frameworks_detected">Frameworks detected</string>
    <string name="app_details_app_information">App information</string>
    <string name="app_details_size">Size</string>
    <string name="app_details_version">Version</string>
    <string name="app_details_target_sdk">Target SDK</string>
    <string name="app_details_min_sdk">Minimum SDK</string>
    <string name="app_details_first_install">First Install</string>
    <string name="app_details_last_update">Last Update</string>
    <string name="app_details_framework_more_files">+ %1$d more files</string>
    <string name="app_details_description">Description</string>
    <string name="app_details_framework_files_found">Files found</string>

    <!--  TECH STACKS  -->
    <string name="tech_stack_flutter_name">Flutter</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_flutter_description">Created by Google, Flutter uses the Dart language to compile directly to native machine code for high performance. It renders its UI using its own graphics engine (Impeller/Skia), ensuring exceptionally smooth, 60fps+ animations across platforms. This architecture makes it highly efficient, though it results in slightly larger initial binary sizes.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_react_native_name">React Native</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_react_native_description">Developed by Meta, React Native utilizes JavaScript or TypeScript to bridge with native platform UI components. It offers solid rendering speed for standard apps, though heavy computational tasks can introduce latency due to the JavaScript-to-native bridge. It remains highly efficient for rapid cross-platform development thanks to its massive ecosystem.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_jetpack_compose_name">Jetpack Compose</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_jetpack_compose_description">Created by Google, Jetpack Compose is Android\'s modern, declarative UI toolkit written entirely in Kotlin. It runs natively on Android with exceptional efficiency, eliminating XML layout overhead through a compiler-optimized runtime. It delivers fast rendering speeds and deep system integration, though it is fundamentally restricted to Android for native builds.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_xamarin_name">Xamarin / .NET MAUI</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_xamarin_description">Developed by Microsoft, Xamarin (now .NET MAUI) utilizes C# and the .NET framework to build cross-platform apps. It achieves near-native performance by compiling directly to native binaries on iOS and using an optimized virtual machine on Android. It is highly efficient for enterprise environments heavily invested in the Microsoft ecosystem.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_cordova_name">Cordova / Ionic / Capacitor</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_cordova_description">Originating from Adobe/Apache, this suite (including Ionic and Capacitor) wraps web technologies like HTML, CSS, and JavaScript inside a native container. It relies on the system\'s WebView, which results in lower performance and slower execution speeds compared to compiled frameworks. It is highly efficient for development speed but poorly suited for resource-intensive applications.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_nativescript_name">NativeScript</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_nativescript_description">Created by Progress (Telerik) and now community-driven, NativeScript allows developers to use JavaScript, TypeScript, or Angular/Vue to build cross-platform apps. It features direct, bridge-free access to native APIs, which provides better performance and speed than standard web-view wrappers. While efficient for leveraging web skills, its UI thread can occasionally bottleneck during heavy processing.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_unity_name">Unity Engine</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_unity_description">Created by Unity Technologies, this powerful cross-platform game engine primarily uses C# for scripting. It is heavily optimized for real-time graphics, delivering exceptional execution speed and rendering efficiency for gaming and interactive simulations. While incredibly performant for multimedia, its runtime overhead makes it less efficient for lightweight, standard UI-driven applications.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_unreal_engine_name">Unreal Engine</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_unreal_engine_description">Developed by Epic Games, Unreal Engine uses C++ and a visual scripting system called Blueprints to deliver industry-leading performance. It is heavily optimized for high-end 3D graphics and complex logic, offering exceptional speed at the cost of high battery and resource consumption. Due to its massive runtime engine size, it is inefficient for traditional, text-based mobile applications.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_godot_name">Godot Engine</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_godot_description">Developed by the Godot community as an open-source project, this lightweight game engine uses GDScript, C#, and C++. It is remarkably fast and lightweight, offering high graphics efficiency with a tiny engine footprint compared to its larger competitors. It balances performance perfectly for 2D and mid-tier 3D mobile games.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_compose_multiplatform_name">Compose Multiplatform</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_compose_multiplatform_description">Developed by JetBrains based on Google\'s Jetpack Compose, this framework shares declarative UIs across Android, iOS, desktop, and web using Kotlin. It compiles directly to native code and utilizes Skiko to render the UI canvas, matching Flutter\'s smooth rendering speeds. It provides excellent development efficiency by allowing complete UI and logic sharing across platforms.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_kotlin_multiplatform_name">Kotlin Multiplatform</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_kotlin_multiplatform_description">Created by JetBrains, Kotlin Multiplatform allows sharing business logic across iOS and Android using Kotlin while keeping the UI completely native. Because it compiles to native binaries, it runs at 100% native speed with zero runtime bridge overhead. It offers maximum performance efficiency, though developers must write platform-specific UIs unless paired with Compose.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_tauri_name">Tauri Mobile</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_tauri_description">Developed by the Tauri community, Tauri Mobile brings its lightweight desktop architecture to mobile using Rust for backend logic and standard web technologies for the frontend. It bypasses heavy runtimes by utilizing the system\'s native WebView, resulting in incredibly small binary sizes and high efficiency. Performance is fast for UI tasks, though data passing between JavaScript and Rust can introduce minor overhead.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_svelte_native_name">Svelte Native</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_svelte_native_description">Developed as a community-driven project, Svelte Native combines the Svelte web framework with NativeScript to produce mobile apps. It utilizes JavaScript or TypeScript but compiles the UI at build time, eliminating a virtual DOM to achieve faster execution speeds and lower memory consumption. It provides highly efficient performance compared to standard hybrid frameworks by directly manipulating native mobile widgets.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_titanium_name">Titanium SDK</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_titanium_description">Created by Appcelerator, Titanium SDK uses JavaScript to map directly to native iOS and Android user interface components. It executes via a JavaScript runtime on the device, offering decent rendering speed but suffering from performance drops during intensive data processing. While efficient for rapid prototyping in the early mobile era, its ecosystem and modern adoption have significantly diminished.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_qt_name">Qt</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_qt_description">Developed by The Qt Company and the Qt Project, Qt is a cross-platform framework that utilizes C++ and QML. It compiles directly to native machine code, delivering blazing-fast speeds, high rendering performance, and exceptional memory efficiency suitable for embedded systems and mobile apps alike. However, its heavy C++ foundation can result in a steeper learning curve and larger application binaries.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_kivy_name">Kivy</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_kivy_description">Created by the Kivy Organization, Kivy is an open-source Python library for developing multi-touch application software. It relies on OpenGL ES 2 for graphics rendering, ensuring fast, GPU-accelerated UI performance across Android, iOS, and desktop. However, because it bundles a Python interpreter, application startup times can be slow, and binary sizes are relatively large and less memory-efficient.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_beeware_name">BeeWare</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_beeware_description">Developed by the BeeWare community, this suite of tools allows developers to write native mobile apps using Python. Unlike frameworks that use a webview or custom canvas, BeeWare compiles Python code to run against actual native OS widgets, aiming for true native look and feel. While execution speed is bounded by the Python interpreter on mobile, it offers excellent development efficiency for Python developers.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_rubymotion_name">RubyMotion</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_rubymotion_description">Created by HipByte, RubyMotion allows developers to write native iOS and Android apps using the Ruby language. It compiles Ruby code directly into native machine binaries using an LLVM-based compiler, delivering true native execution speed and full access to platform APIs without a performance bridge. However, it is a commercial product with a niche community, affecting its modern development efficiency.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_native_name">Native (XML Java/Kotlin)</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_native_description">Rooted in the official Android development standards by Google, this approach uses Java or Kotlin alongside XML for layout design. It offers the absolute highest performance, execution speed, and battery efficiency possible because it runs directly on the Android runtime without translation layers. While it lacks cross-platform code sharing, it provides zero-latency access to device hardware and the smallest possible binary overhead.</string>

    <string name="tech_stack_unknown_name">Unknown</string>
    <string name="tech_stack_unknown_description">This placeholder represents an unidentified or unsupported technology stack within the analyzer\'s codebase. It possesses no specific origin, language framework, or performance metrics until the underlying code can be properly resolved. It is utilized purely for error handling and fallback categorization.</string>

    <!--  DEVICE INFO SCREEN  -->
    <string name="device_info_title">Device info</string>
    <string name="device_unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="device_value_unavailable">N/A</string>
    <string name="device_add_to_home">Add to Home screen</string>
    <string name="device_added_to_home">Added to Home screen</string>

    <string name="device_tab_system">System</string>
    <string name="device_tab_cpu">CPU</string>
    <string name="device_tab_battery">Battery</string>
    <string name="device_tab_sensors">Sensors</string>
    <string name="device_tab_memory">Memory</string>
    <string name="device_tab_display">Display</string>

    <!--  System tab  -->
    <string name="device_system_manufacturer">Manufacturer</string>
    <string name="device_system_brand">Brand</string>
    <string name="device_system_model">Model</string>
    <string name="device_system_device">Device</string>
    <string name="device_system_board">Board</string>
    <string name="device_system_hardware">Hardware</string>
    <string name="device_system_android_version">Android version</string>
    <string name="device_system_security_patch">Security patch</string>
    <string name="device_system_build">Build</string>
    <string name="device_system_kernel">Kernel</string>

    <!--  CPU tab  -->
    <string name="device_cpu_soc">SoC</string>
    <string name="device_cpu_abis">Supported ABIs</string>
    <string name="device_cpu_cores">Cores</string>
    <string name="device_cpu_usage">CPU usage</string>
    <string name="device_cpu_clock_speeds">Clock speeds</string>
    <string name="device_cpu_core_x">Core %1$d</string>
    <string name="device_cpu_temperatures">Temperatures</string>

    <!--  Battery tab  -->
    <string name="device_battery_ampere_title">Current draw</string>
    <string name="device_battery_charging_now">Charging</string>
    <string name="device_battery_discharging_now">Discharging</string>
    <string name="device_battery_current_unavailable">Not reported by this device</string>
    <string name="device_battery_level">Level</string>
    <string name="device_battery_status">Status</string>
    <string name="device_battery_health">Health</string>
    <string name="device_battery_technology">Technology</string>
    <string name="device_battery_power_source">Power source</string>
    <string name="device_battery_voltage">Voltage</string>
    <string name="device_battery_temperature">Temperature</string>
    <string name="device_battery_power">Power</string>
    <string name="device_battery_capacity">Capacity</string>
    <string name="device_battery_cycle_count">Cycle count</string>
    <string name="device_battery_session_min">Session min</string>
    <string name="device_battery_session_max">Session max</string>

    <string name="device_battery_status_charging">Charging</string>
    <string name="device_battery_status_discharging">Discharging</string>
    <string name="device_battery_status_full">Full</string>
    <string name="device_battery_status_not_charging">Not charging</string>
    <string name="device_battery_health_good">Good</string>
    <string name="device_battery_health_overheat">Overheating</string>
    <string name="device_battery_health_dead">Dead</string>
    <string name="device_battery_health_over_voltage">Over voltage</string>
    <string name="device_battery_health_cold">Cold</string>
    <string name="device_battery_plugged_ac">AC charger</string>
    <string name="device_battery_plugged_usb">USB</string>
    <string name="device_battery_plugged_wireless">Wireless</string>
    <string name="device_battery_plugged_unplugged">Unplugged</string>

    <!--  Sensors tab  -->
    <string name="device_sensor_vendor">Vendor</string>
    <string name="device_sensor_value">Value</string>
    <string name="device_sensor_other">Sensor</string>

    <!--  Memory tab  -->
    <string name="device_memory_ram">RAM</string>
    <string name="device_memory_storage">Storage</string>
    <string name="device_memory_total">Total</string>
    <string name="device_memory_used">Used</string>
    <string name="device_memory_available">Available</string>

    <!--  Display tab  -->
    <string name="device_display_resolution">Resolution</string>
    <string name="device_display_density">Density</string>
    <string name="device_display_refresh_rate">Refresh rate</string>
    <string name="device_display_size">Screen size</string>
</resources>